Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Hey everybody, how are you?
How are you?
I've been home and having a snack!
So here we are...
I hope everyone has gathered here.
Today is December
I would like to do a birthday party with you all, as I turned 19 years old today.
Yay!
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
So, have you all gathered?
Did they come? I don't know.
Well, maybe that's it. You can't see the chat on YouTube.
The chat has gone dark on the chat.
I'd like you to turn it on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my friend?
I don't know what's going on.
Can you guys see me?
Can you see me?
I see you on Twitter and in the fan club, and in the comments.
Happy Birthday!
Thank you. This is the fan club.
Camera.
So...
Are you ready to go?
Shall we go?
Okay, birthday party for everyone.
We'll have cake and juice.
We'll have some juice, too.
Yes, please.
Everyone, please.
Sing the song.
Indeed it is.
Kitty, you're going home.
Oh, I could see this one.
Please sing along, everyone.
Okay, I'll go now.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
What's wrong?
My shoulder hurts.
Oh, no, no, no.
Congratulations.
Hey, this time you always connect with your dad, right?
Yeah.
All these flew away.
They flew away.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all for coming back.
Hey, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
You're early.
Happy Birthday tomorrow!
I turned 19.
Happy birthday to you.
Last teenager.
Last peep.
Last peepee.
Look how delicious.
Yum! Yum!
I'm getting close to all kinds of keys.
I can't see them.
Can I have the toy?
That was a blast.
Was it a blast?
It was a blast.
I love you guys.
He's so cute.
Christmas tree.
It's adorable.
Oh, it's true.
And since it's almost May, we'll have a Christmas tree.
Hey, a tree, too.
Please take it.
It's so cute
Lively
So cute!
OK, the suits are all here.
Wait for the moon!
What? Cute!
Wait!
Cute!
Oh, it's so cute!
Thank you!
Oh, it's so cute! Cute!
Oh, it's so cute!
Is it really cute?
It's a cute snowman.
Here you go.
It's cute.
Cute.
Snowman.
He's so cute.
They keep looking at each other.
He's cute.
What is it?
Cute.
Hey, scary.
It's cute.
It looks like everyone bought a lot.
Yes, yes...
Well, let's have a toast.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
All right. - All right.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you guys for making the cake so pretty.
Gentian cake.
Delicious!
So, 19-year-old Shizui, please give my best wishes to you.
Cheers!
Cheers. - Cheers.
Cheers.
I'd like to propose a toast.
I'll drink to that.
Cheers.
It's cold and delicious.
Delicious.
Eh, too cute
My hair's getting big.
Hey!
It's so hot!
I took a look.
So cute!
This length is so cute, I just curl it around my head and make one curve.
Cute.
Then, let's eat it!
Oh, sister, you're still eating it.
Bon appétit!
What kind of ruins are these?
I wonder.
I heard there are some tissues in there.
Certainly here.
Oh, marshmallows.
I thought this was different sugar.
I don't detect any sugar.
It's not marzipan.
Look, it's sugar.
I'd like to put it in my tea. It doesn't look like it floats.
It's absolutely adorable.
I'm afraid of HH.
Bon appétit.
Let's all eat together.
Let's eat it alone.
Let's eat together
Bon appétit!
Chocolate.
What is it?
What's this?
Oh, my God!
What is it?
Mousse?
It's mousse.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's so cute. It's so cute.
What's this? It's coconut.
It's coconut all around.
It's coconut. It's delicious.
Coconut?
Coconut is delicious. The snow-like thing is coconut.
This is mousse.
Cheesecake!
It looks like cheesecake mousse.
Cheesecake mousse.
It's so delicious.
Cheese mousse. Delicious coconut.
Today, Haru-chan and I are changing checks.
Yes.
This cream is delicious.
And the mask is delicious.
What's with the background music?
What's that? It's true.
Hey.
Serif, serif, serif.
Something interesting.
Something's here.
Something's funny
Happy birthday to you
What?
Is he here?
It's here.
Here it comes.
This cake is going to be a lady.
It's delicious.
You can see the beanbags, too.
Sweetie, you're eating from behind.
I said from the front. It's so miserable.
They all look so good. Delicious.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my neck's broken.
It's sugar, right?
Sugar?
It's hard.
I cut it off.
Found it.
It's so cute.
This is food, right?
Yes, it is.
It's cute.
Cute, cute, cute.
Let's just stick together for a second.
Okay.
Go back.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's good.
Do we have to buy this stuff?
I kind of like the egg thing.
Well, I'm just getting started.
It's good.
Hmm?
Oh, orange?
Orange.
Yeah, orange.
Delicious.
Sara.
Hey, it's Sara.
It's so good.
Yes, it is.
We celebrated with a Hurt Cake.
It was so good with the strawberries.
It was delicious.
No nose cream today?
Do you want it today?
Maybe no nose cream.
We have a lot of snacks.
Eat.
Diamonds.
You're so cute.
Amenge.
I'll give you two.
How many buttons?
Amunds.
What are these?
Amundschluss.
I don't have any.
I don't have any. This is delicious.
Shingencho
me wasted!
gia
So I would like to find out how to make the cake and go next by myself.
It's about time you all did.
No, what the heck?
I don't think so.
So, I'm going to continue.
It's down!
Yum!
Oh, you say "no".
It's good!
Oh, it's called "Ie-chan.
Oh, yeah!
Don't film me!
Next, I'd like to go to Aki-chan's question and answer session.
Ask me a question!
I'd like to thank all of you
You've sent us your questions in one day, one day.
If you don't have a question, I'll write it here.
I'd like to write them here.
I'm sure you've already got a lot of questions.
I'd better answer a lot of them.
Here we go!
See you later!
Thank you, Mr. and Mrs. Hasaki!
You're always so chic, cute and fashionable, Aki-chan.
What is the next fashion item you are targeting?
Eh, I don't know, what is it?
But you know, Hiyori just gave me a pair of leg warmers.
Yeah, yeah...
They were really cute.
Next time, I'd like to try different leg warmers.
I'll have to cover my legs soon since I'll be sitting in various seats.
But I want them to be visible, right?
Next, Kohayuri!
What is your favorite Suzi story?
This is my favorite.
You know what I mean?
That one, right?
That's it.
Blowfish.
What?
Smile, right?
Blowfish?
I love pufferfish.
If it's puffer fish.
I've had salmon, too.
The price is the price is the price is the price is the price is the price is the price is the price is the price and keep it at the price you want to pay.
Good night.
Sorry, sorry.
But the Haagen-Dazs matcha sandwich ice cream was delicious!
That was delicious!
I think it's the one they're talking about at Seven these days, the caramel one, with the cookie on top, the famous one, that everyone eats...
A collaboration of sweets.
Yes, yes, yes.
You want to twist it?
Caramel's favorite ice cream. It's got some kind of caramel in it.
It's kind of a trocket. I often get it with pictures or words on it.
Yes, yes.
He said that.
And what else?
This ice cream is delicious.
Ice cream?
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
Thank you, Takumi.
I can't stop eating this one, Aki-chan.
What is it?
What is it? What is it?
I can't stop this.
What is it?
I can't stop.
Crab bread.
I keep eating crab bread.
Crab bread reminds me of Aki-chan's face.
At the convenience store.
It's fun.
Continue.
Thank you, Mao!
Aki-chan, if there was snow on the ground, what would you like to do at the end of the day?
Aki-chan's face would be beautiful
What should I do?
I want to go to the snow mountain
Yes, to the snowy mountains.
I want to go.
I want to go with everyone
I really want to go to the snowy mountains.
Oh, no...
What?
Nico!
Which one is it, Nico?
Not at Yukigas'.
He's cute.
Write "Yukigas".
Go on.
Thank you.
Of all the live catering you've eaten this year.
What are you particularly hungry for?
I ate some pretty good food, didn't I?
Yukigas.
Yes, I did.
If there was a little too much catering for me...
I'd like to eat.
The background music might be a little loud.
It's up.
Okay, here we go.
Roast beef!
That was great!
Mr. Kishida gave me a femmes cencer.
This was delicious!
Everything was delicious. The sushi was great, too!
I bought the roast beef and it was delicious!
It was delicious!
That was delicious.
Everything was delicious.
I couldn't resist.
The barbeque bento was delicious.
Oh, the one from the person who won?
The one I won too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's gone.
I'm so happy.
It's not about one or the other.
It's a song about everyone, isn't it?
Today.
Loads of burgers.
Okay, we'll continue.
Oh, thank you, Akito.
If you could go anywhere in Sloane, where would you go?
Back to Japan.
What? If you were in Japan...
Okinawa.
If overseas...
Australia.
Next
Oyoshihito-chan
Akito, what is your favorite Pokemon skill?
By the way, I love Docudoku.
Between your favorite Pokémon?
What is it, like a revolution?
Mio likes...
Hey, thump, thump.
A little bit, your voice, a little bit... you think it's tiny, or it says it's tiny.
I don't know if you can hear me.
I'm about to put the bin mike in.
I thought it was supposed to be easier to hear.
Sorry.
Yes, at a later volume.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, it's true. It's flickering.
Why is that?
Don't you want to dribble a little?
Don't you want it to drip?
I'm a little more.
Is that a resonance? What is it?
Can you hear it?
He says he can hear you now.
I can't hear you. Really?
I'll work on my voice.
Thank you, Sorama-chan.
Is there anything you would like to do before you turn 20, the last year of your teenage years?
Yes, I do.
Something I want to say before I turn 20.
But it's kind of hard to cut hair, isn't it?
I had my coming-of-age ceremony.
So it's pretty short now, and I'm not sure if I'll ever be able to cut it again.
I may not be able to cut it again, but I'd like to keep it short.
It looks good on you.
It looks great.
Thank you, Acchanmaru!
If you could be Doraemon's friend, what would you like to do with his tools?
It's amazing that we can be friends.
I wonder what it would be
I don't know how to do it anywhere.
Or here.
If you open the door, even here.
I'm gonna run as far as I can.
That's the best part.
I'll be asleep in no time.
Next.
Soma...
If you could switch places with another member for one day...
Who would you be and what would you do?
Yes...
If you were to switch places with another member for one day...
You'd be alone, right?
Hmmm...
Then, I'd like to be Julia and lose my bangs.
But would my face change too?
Would your face change to Julia's?
Yes.
Everything will be Julia.
Then you can enjoy your bangs.
Well, I'd like to be anyone.
Really? Are you sure? Sound.
Sound okay?
Are you okay?
Right now, it's like I can't even hear it.
Not anymore.
Cute, cute, cute.
It's okay, isn't it?
But I can't hear you anymore.
It's, you know, it's going through like it's looking at something.
It's my stomach.
Your voice is not helping. Thank you.
It's okay.
I have a normal volume, by the way.
I'm pretty sure he can hear me, too.
Your voice is not helping.
Thank you, Mr. Dirk.
How did you decide on your hair for the show?
My manager decides for me.
There's a no-no today.
I haven't felt like it's a very special day for YouTube.
But a lot of people are.
I heard the background music again.
So many people are supporting me.
I'm so grateful that so many people are supporting me and want to celebrate me, even if it's just a little bit.
Thank you so much!
I applaud you more than Yarubei.
I applaud you more than Yarubei, so that I can do something.
Next.
Thank you, Renanan.
On the day of your birthday, what did you have for breakfast?
Um, I ate rice with taro.
Oh, that's good.
I had a pithy medal at the end.
That's good.
Next.
I'll make it three more.
This is my third.
Thank you, Named Rabbit.
What are your aspirations for your 19th year?
Well, 19-year-olds, you know, that kind of thing,
Eh? I don't know.
What are your aspirations for the 19th year?
To be the day when I can keep moving and talking forever, without stopping anymore.
I'll do my best.
Not at all, Dantie, thank you.
Sorry for the mystery, it's like a one-person delivery.
It's okay, everyone's eating cake.
It's ok everyone is eating cake
Nattee-san
What is your favorite new song released this year?
This year?
This year.
La Bou
Laboo is still delicious.
Laboo.
I love it. It's so cute.
I love it, it's so cute.
Thank you so much for the next one.
What is your role on stage or in dramas as a 19-year-old?
I really, really love anime, so I'm hoping to do a live-action version or something someday.
Next, Mr. Knights Phi. Thank you, Night's Phi.
Which do you like better, baked pudding or regular pudding?
I like hard baked pudding.
What about baked pudding?
Why everyone?
Wait one more time.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Chico.
What's your favorite hairstyle right now?
Half twin.
It's cute.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Hello, omake.
Who was the first to receive a congratulatory message?
The quiz was, of all the members, but this time they were all very fast.
Everyone was very fast. Everyone, everyone was fast.
Who was fast?
That one.
I messed up.
I did it, too.
I was fast.
Out of all the members, who came in first?
Ta-da-da-da-da-da.
Ta-da!
Hiyori.
You're a stickler, aren't you?
Blah, blah, blah.
But you know, Kizuna is even better.
Really? Was it fast?
But everyone was fast.
I was like 4 minutes.
Five minutes.
I thought, "Oh no.
If I did something wrong, I'd be a big baby.
I was fast.
But I was really slow.
I was rather slow, too.
But you were so flexible. Before I went to bed.
Everyone was here, and they were returning things, but...
What? Why? Why?
Some of them.
I got a reply back from one of them.
I didn't get a reply.
You're kidding?
I delivered it.
We're back in business, Carami.
You're kidding?
It's definitely her.
What?
You're sure?
It's too funny.
I'm pretty sure he returned them in order.
Why?
I was too late. They got tired of it.
Oh, what? I'm sorry.
But you were 12?
I'm sorry, 12 is too young, but it's too dark.
It's kind of hard to tell, isn't it?
We're all, like, 10 years old.
Oh, sorry.
It's been like 20 minutes.
I don't know. Maybe it's the main one.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was pretty honest with you.
That honest?
Why, why, why?
Why so much?
Well, you know, I should... I should...
Why not?
Because my birthday's in... in four hours.
No way.
No way. Tears.
Why? Why?
Where's Pio?
Ask me in 10 years.
Ask me in 10 years?
There it is.
It's perfect.
And, you know, I thought he was pretty strong.
Heh.
You're rigorous.
You pulled off a move like this.
You don't have to say that for the long haul.
You're doing awful.
Rigorous.
That's unusual.
You haven't said anything back.
I'm not getting any replies.
It's a piece fake.
Yori saw it.
I'm the first to notice.
Yorichan saw it.
She got tired of it and came back in a dream
Yes, in a dream.
She came back to the studio telepathically.
Yes, yes.
I heard she was naturally hurt.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm back. That's such a bad idea.
Aki-chan's busy.
It's all my fault.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
It's not my fault.
Let's go next time.
Let's go next.
What do we do now?
You know, when I do this to this guy, I feel sorry for him.
It's like I made him cry.
Are you done?
I'm done.
He's laughing about next year.
That was so funny.
I can't wait to see Tsukada-san.
I'm so, so, so happy.
But Cat-sama is white
I see, I'm waiting for the angel.
I already had the cheese juice.
Quite a bit.
Akichan can't help it.
I just got your comment.
Let's move on.
Thanks for the mini-rabbit.
Aki-chan, good question.
If you want to get warm, do you prefer a futon or a kotatsu?
I like to get into a futon with cold clothes.
I prefer futons.
You don't have to apologize only for why.
Next, please give me the IQ 5-point set of Pippan-chan Ainu and 19-year-old Aki-chan, who is too cute.
IQ 5-Piece Set
Smile
Crescent Moon
What do you say?
Me.
Akio loves pen sets, everyone loves them.
Yes.
Next, Koshieki-chan, thank you.
Aki-chan loves Hiyorin, but because of Hiyorin's hiyori, she switched places with Hiyorin.
Now, what are you going to do?
With Pamplin.
That's so funny.
You're acting like Pamplin.
What's that? Pamplin'?
Like Papryn.
Hey, you know, today...
Just a little Paplin. He's resting a little.
Good night.
Papryn, I'm taking a little vacation.
Pappulin vacation?
I've been working so hard sometimes.
I've been working so hard.
I've been working so hard. I've been working so hard.
Three more, including now.
Three more, then.
To open Hiorin's store.
I already have.
I'm singing too.
I'm listening to my voice.
Next, MUTTA.
What is your next goal if you succeed in the TMG selection split?
Yes, that's right.
This year I was able to go to Indonesia,
I would like to do my best so that more and more people will be able to participate,
I will do my best so that we can expand our business worldwide.
I will do my best.
Oh, I can't do it.
Oh, so it's the last one.
Last! Rust!
I did it again, Rust! Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you, Yukihime!
How long did it take you to blow dry your hair before you cut it?
Has it changed now that it's this length?
Before I cut my hair, I used to use the dryer for about 20 minutes.
Oh, that's right.
I'm so tired...
I return my face right after taking a bath so it's still wet, so it takes about 20 minutes, but now it takes about 10 minutes.
Wow!
Now it's about 100 minutes.
That's such a difference. It's amazing.
So that's the end of the hair questions, and that's all for now.
Thank you very much.
I don't know if I laughed that much in the corner.
I'm not sorry anymore.
Thank you very much.
Yes, let's go.
Already.
It's already done. Aki-chan is the star of the show.
I'm looking forward to it.
So, first of all, I hope you are interested in this event,
I would like to introduce some goods.
First of all, here it is.
Jeez! It's filled with water! This way! Jajan!
Fresh photo!
Oh, my!
How do I look?
Cute!
So cute!
I went with pink and a uniform this time.
It's so cute!
So cute!
Since I'm a teenager, I wore my school uniform.
I love it! It's so cute!
It's a little messy and distracting.
It's cute.
Namachu's recommendation?
Oh, yeah, that's my favorite!
It's so cute!
I recommend like #437!
So cute!
I chose all of the live photos myself this time, and I thought about which one I would choose,
I'd be happy if everyone could get a lot of them.
Cute.
Cute?
So cute.
It would be cuter if it was on Instagram.
I think it would be cuter if it was on Instagram.
There are things that only Instagram can do.
Cute.
Number 427.
It's so hot.
Awesome.
Thank you.
And your outfit is adorable.
Pink.
I got pink.
I'm in love with pink.
I'm in love with all things pink these days.
Pink club
Pink is so cute.
It's so cute.
Pancakes are so cute.
Yes, the pancakes have Aki-chan's happy pastiche in them!
That's amazing.
These cakes are popular in Korea, aren't they?
Yes, yes, yes.
So cute.
It's cute.
I chose them with a lot of care, so please take a look.
Take a look.
And next, Kumichan Opuzi!
Yay!
Oh, Kumichan Opuzi.
I have something I've missed.
Everyone's lekki mode is so cute.
It's so good.
I might want to get that.
It's so cute. It's really cute.
Really?
I want to go to K-1 for the file.
It's so cute.
I might want one.
Everyone's keychain.
I want it on the back of my train.
So if you guys don't know me...
You should buy one.
I picked out all the files for you.
Good luck.
It's so cute!
Look at this.
It's a version of the mecerary from earlier.
So cute!
Cute.
Tweet
I've got a lot of energy, so I'm going to show it off with a badge.
I'm going to tweet about it.
A tweet, you mean.
Good night.
What's this? Oh, my God.
I thought I'd have everyone write down their goals,
Four boxes of four different kinds.
Is this really that big?
I'm sure they are.
Are you getting them?
This is my tweet.
Can you see it?
Wait a minute.
It's a tweet with a lot of words on it.
And here is a QR code,
It's a QR code,
It's a thank you to all of you.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
I'll eat it now.
This way.
The QR corner for fans is awesome, though.
Yes, it is.
Thanks for making the congratulatory posters.
For example, if your name is Strawberry, please make it easy to enjoy again by saying Sudai Chigo, and I will do my best.
This is my goal for this year. My goals are also written there.
My goal for Sudai Chigo for 19 years old is, first, to be able to cut the members with a seed.
Now that you have written down your goals for where you are, please write down your goals as well and use them.
Choushi, thank you. It's so cute. I spent a lot of time thinking about it.
Please use it.
Your eyes are so cute.
It's interesting, isn't it?
I'd love to see that too.
Please do it.
After that, they are going to start selling at 9:00 p.m.
Oh, that's about an hour away.
Yes, and then the last.
I'd be happy if you all could wait for me.
Oh.
Ladies and gentlemen, my laundry products.
Oh, my goodness.
This time, bangs.
Pins. I made it into a bangs clip.
It's so cute.
It comes in a set of bangs clips and stickers,
The outfit is designed to be chibi-me,
The costume is designed for a little girl, but I had them make her face into the face I like to wear,
I also had the costume made into the Timoreaux's Strongest Costume, which is my favorite costume.
Aki-chan likes to wear Timorow's best costume.
So, I made her look like this,
It's so cute.
It will be the most memorable costume for me.
I did it.
It's cute.
I'm going to make this set with bangs and this set, or this set with bangs and this set,
There are two patterns, so please check them out.
Cute.
I don't have electric expenses.
No, we don't have it yet.
It's about this much. Bangs clip.
It's about this much, and it can definitely be used when you want to wash your face without bangs, so please buy one.
I like it.
The speckers are small enough to fit in the back of a cell phone, and they are really cute, so please check them out.
Please check it out.
It might be fun if you don't buy it.
Get it.
Get it, get it, get it.
So, that's all for now.
Goods?
Goods, you know.
All of them will be on sale at 9:00 p.m., so please check them out!
And last but not least
Last but not least, I tried my hand at singing again this year!
I haven't told anyone yet.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm a bit embarrassed to say, but I wasn't too convinced when I was recording the song.
I finished the whole song, but then I had to start all over again.
It was a very annoying thing to do.
But I did my best, and I'm glad you listened to it.
Please listen to the song.
Please listen to it.
Wow!
It looks good on you.
It's too good.
Evangelion.
I love the anime, and I'm also a secret fan, and it became the theme song for it, and I got the cruel pages theme out of it.
It's amazing!
I thought I was going to be your guest.
But it went up at midnight yesterday.
I thought it would be nice to invite a lot of people, so I met with two of them.
I'm so glad you got to see so much of it.
They are super cute.
It's more interesting in the middle.
It's wonderful.
Everyone, everyone.
A new frontier.
Really came out of the cartoon like you.
Really amazing.
Really too cute.
It's amazing. The possibilities are endless.
It's amazing.
What time is it later?
9:00? - 9:00? Maybe 9:00?
It will be on TOKI's YouTube channel, so please check it out.
You're looking great today, MeMeMeMe.
She's so cute.
Okay, I'll leave it at that.
Isn't that the next one?
I was really looking forward to it.
Oh, you said you wanted butter.
May I?
Let's see what you have to say.
Are you stupid?
You're so cute!
I'd like to go next.
Next up, number four.
Let's give Aki-chan a present!
I'm looking forward to seeing what everyone will draw.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Yes, ma'am.
So cute!
Three, two, one.
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors.
It's aiko, right?
Aiko, right?
Everybody, ah, to the three who won.
First, goo, rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, I'll go first.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Okay, I'll go first.
Happy pie, Aki-chan!
Congratulations.
What do you think?
It's fun to see it like this.
I wonder what it is.
What if we're all crabby?
I'd be happy.
I'm glad you're here. It's going to be a long case.
I'll be waiting for you every day.
Wait, I think I might have figured it out.
Oh, I'm glad.
You're cute. I'm glad.
Oh, he's cute.
It's cute.
I'm going to make slippers this time.
I'm going to make new slippers because last year's slippers are falling apart.
Wanna wear them for everyday?
They are so cute.
I'll wear them at home.
I'm glad. You know, there are people who wear them and people who don't wear them.
So I was wondering which one it was, but they were so cute that I fell in love with even the pink ones.
Oh, there!
Yes, a little bit.
So cute!
But after I take a bath.
After you get cleaned up.
I'll think about it.
Thank you! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy about the bath!
You're so cute!
Baths and butts are so cute.
I'm so happy!
I want you to see it! So cute!
Looks good on you, Aki-chan.
It's so fluffy!
So cute!
Next is Pio.
Thank you.
Cute.
A sentence.
See you later.
Aki-chan, would you like to read it?
Oh, it's long.
Very long.
I'll read it. Happy birthday, Aki-chan.
Thank you.
My 19th birthday present is..,
Cute!
I got you a bunny purse.
Oh my gosh, that's so cute!
It's so cute!
It's pink.
You know me.
I wanted you to have something cute like this no matter how old you are.
I think it's perfect for when you're going on an expedition, or when you have a big bag.
I hope it makes you happy just to have it.
I hope you eat a lot of it!
And here's a little something extra.
Now there's only one Christmas clip left!
Isn't it cute?
For the Christmas lover, Akiteyan.
Vitamins, right?
Akite-yan!
Enjoy your teenage last wear!
Let's keep loving each other as neighbors!
More than
Thank you more than
I'll love love love you.
So cute!
They're all so cute.
You look like Aki-chan.
I'm so happy.
Where did you come from?
I'm just going to use this as a bag.
It's so cute! It's so fluffy and comfy!
It's true!
It's so cute!
Thank you, Iori!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy! Keep up the good work, Aktyan!
Akutyan!
I'll do my best! Thank you!
I like the green onion case!
It's so cute!
Thank you!
Usa-chan is so cute!
It would be so cute if it was on the back garling when I was on the train.
I'd feel sorry for him on the train, too.
She looks like a pet!
Name it
It's me.
I went for the relaxing type.
I finished slowly.
That helps.
I moved a lot.
Thank you. - Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Next time?
I like this simulation that you joined five times.
I can see that.
What? Something collagen cold.
That's a new one.
New?
I want to see how it looks.
I'm glad. I've been feeling a little dry lately.
Still a little dry.
A little collagen.
Because I think I've never seen it before.
Sweaty type
Thanks for the pink.
pink is cute!
I'm glad you like pink.
I think I've never seen it before
It's new.
It's a herbal tea.
Thank you very much.
It's got some good stuff in it.
I love Kurmame.
It's delicious.
It's kind of...
I got to taste it.
I'm here for the tasting.
It's delicious.
This is it! It's like a granberry and ginger. It's so good for your throat.
It's so good!
I'll drink it when I get it today.
Thank you.
I'll buy some.
Delicious.
I like the berth.
It's very attractive.
Very cool
Focus on the view
I'm next.
Oh, okay.
Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday!
Well, I was wondering if I got two bags of something...
Oh...
I'll switch.
I'll put it in this one.
Looks so good!
I told them I was going to be in Yokohama for a year.
I made it Yokohama's.
This is also from Yokohama.
I see.
Looks delicious!
I wrote "looks delicious".
Looks delicious.
Puzzle chocolates?
This is for Christmas, Aki-chan. Sorry, not pink.
I'm sorry, it's not pink. I know you like Christmas, so I thought this chocolate looked good.
Puzzle? It's a chocolate tree puzzle.
So cute!
Looks so good, I want some.
Eat it.
Let's eat. I'm so happy.
Chocolate is so good.
And it looks delicious.
And here...
Is this some kind of bread-making chocolate?
It says "chocolate that makes bread taste good.
I love chocolate chocolate! Thank you!
There are three different flavors.
You can put this on fruit.
I was told that this chocolate can be dipped in fruit.
You can put it on fruit.
I think it looks really sweet!
You should buy some when you go to Yokohama!
What's that?
It's a puzzle.
It's a puzzle?
It's so cute!
I'm going to eat it. I'm going to eat it.
I'm putting it together.
Maybe. I don't know.
I don't know.
I'll drink it later.
I'll have some.
I'll try it.
Thank you.
Happy chocolate.
It's good.
That's good.
Here.
If it were early, I might be talking fast.
About another hour.
Thank you, Juro-chan.
What's that?
It's got an expiration date on it.
Plums lose, too.
Which one do you want first?
Okay, the freebie.
What's a little extra?
Really?
There's an expiration date on it.
Tomorrow?
Okay, I'll have one.
Oh! This is really...
Wait.
Here's what's inside.
Ansei's deliciousness!
Super tasty!
I'm addicted to clocks!
The strawberry one.
He's got so much stuff!
Delicious!
It's so good!
You have so many!
One per bag
Yes, yes, yes.
It's so good.
I'll eat it!
Everyone is getting ready to go.
A little less interesting this time around.
Cute.
Oh, it's so cute!
It's like Christmas!
Ta-da-da-da!
Ew!
So cute.
Like ornaments?
Ah! Brasagal!
No, wait, really!
It's something that hangs around in the store!
That's what Mr. Puan is looking at!
Oh, that's so cute!
Is that the one on the side?
Hand cream?
Oh, thank you, I was really dry!
It smells so good!
That's it.
Oh, it's really cute?
Is that gel really cute?
Is it really cute?
Bye-bye!
Cute.
It's so cute.
Oh, my God.
Cute!
It's pretty darn cute.
I'm so happy.
Here, like this.
Like this.
Like this
Cute.
Like a cucumber.
It's got a great movement.
So cute.
Take it off. Hand cream.
Thank you.
It's a picture of Santa Claus.
That's so Santa!
Like this.
Ainori.
Thank you very much.
It's really chilly.
I hate it.
Take it off.
It's disgusting.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
That was nice.
How's the pretty one?
It was cute.
But, you know, it made me happy.
This is like a house.
No, it was cute.
The scary ones were scary too.
But, you know, I'm happy.
I'm happy. And seeing new things.
I was happy.
So, thank you all.
Congratulations.
Already, yes, welcome back.
Congratulations. I'm glad. You did a great job.
So, that's it.
Let's do a final decision-making scrub together.
Let's do it.
So, let's start with Aki-chan.
Aki-chan.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
When is it?
Koukou.
Yes.
Good night.
OK? OK? Four, three, two, one, zero.
OK!
Let's all get a shot!
Take a picture!
I got it.
Actually, I think I'm gonna choke.
I'm talking too much.
I'm talking so much, I'm almost choking.
Oh, yeah, definitely get a shot of the cheese.
Okay, good night.
Okay, thank you very much.
Let's get a cheeseburger.
Cheeky, cheeky, cheeky, cheeky, cheeky.
Come on.
Cheese.
Cheese, cheese.
So many!
Yes, cheese.
Yes, last.
OK!
Yes. Is it hidden?
That's the one.
Yes, a little bit.
This way.
Here it is.
TikTok Project
Hashtag
Toki-chan Aki-chan Birthday
with the hashtag "Aki-chan Birthday!
Aki-chan's birthday video on TikTok
to those who post a video on TikTok with Toki-chan's song
to those who post their favorite videos on TikTok with Toki-chan's music.
Aki-chan's favorite things and
your desire to be too cute.
Please make a video of it!
This is what I'm asking you to do.
We drew a lot of winners from among the contributors.
I just took this for you a while ago.
We would like to give away the following to six people.
When you post your video, please use the hashtag
hashtag and Akichan Akichan Birthday.
and add the hashtag "Kichan Aki-chan Birthday" to your post.
I would be very happy if you could upload my cute and adorable video.
The contest will be open until January 3rd.
New Year's Day?
Yes.
About 13 more days?
Two weeks?
Two weeks! Good luck, everyone.
I hope you can make it happen!
Please.
There are a lot of them.
Congratulations!
Aki-chan has one last thing to say.
So, this is it,
Sudaiko-san turned 19!
Sudaiko!
Congratulations!
I am so grateful to know that so many people are supporting me even when I post on Instagram.
I heard that some people put up posters in Shibuya and Osaka, and some people put up posters at Palpo in Ikebukuro, etc. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. I came to see the show. I would be very happy if I could see everyone smiling,
I will do my best to make everyone who is involved with me smile, not just the two of you.
So, yes.
I am glad that you are watching over me, Aki-chan. Please do.
When should we start watching today?
Now is the metal.
Did you say something?
Yes, I did.
Thanks for all your contributions, I couldn't read much of it earlier.
Thank you very much.
Have fun, Yuki-kun.
I'm looking forward to your visit.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I will.
I can't remember what I was going to say.
I can't remember what I was going to say anymore.
Oh, that's right. After this, we're going to do an after-posting broadcast in the fan club. You know, this is it.
So please watch it too. Please do.
Okay, so I'm 19 years old. You know, when I was 18, I thought that I hated my birthday so much,
But I was able to greet my 19th birthday with a very happy feeling. Please continue to look forward to the 19-year-old Aki Suda.
So, thank you very much for watching until the end. Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Thank you for watching.